lifestorage.com 2019-05-30

# Life Storage Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to your use of the Life Storage LP website located at www.lifestorage.com (the "Site"), which is comprised of various web pages and is owned and operated by Life Storage LP, and the Life Storage LP services available through the Site ("Services"). This Privacy Policy describes how Life Storage LP and its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively, "Life Storage") collect and use the information you provide on or through the Site. 

This Privacy Policy also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your information and how you can access and update your information. You acknowledge that this Privacy Policy is part of Life Storage's Terms of Use ("Terms") and by accessing or using the Site, you agree to be bound by both this Privacy Policy and the Terms. If you do not agree to abide by both this Privacy Policy and the Terms, please do not use the Site.

#### Collection and Use of Personal Information

When you become a Life Storage customer, we may collect the following information from you:

  * Contact information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number.
  * Billing information such as credit card number, and billing address.
  * Rental facility information such as space number and gate/access code.
  * Other information as requested.

We may use your information to:

  * Process your payments.
  * Send you information about your use of the Life Storage Services, purchases and other transactions.
  * Respond to your customer service requests.
  * Administer your account.
  * Communicate with you about current offers or events.

#### Information Sharing

We may share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy. We do not sell your information to third parties. We may provide your information to our contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business and who only are authorized to use your information as necessary for the purposes for which we disclose your information to them. For example, all financial and billing information collected through the Site is used solely to invoice customers for their usage of Life Storage products and services. This billing information is not used by Life Storage for marketing and/or promotional purposes. We may also disclose your information in the following circumstances:

  * As required by law or where there is lawful basis to disclose information, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process.
  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.
  * If we have obtained your prior consent to do so.

In order to improve our business, we may buy or sell a company, or one or more of the companies in our corporate family may merge with or be acquired by another company. If we sell a business, we may transfer some or all of your information as a part of the sale. In the event we transfer any of your information in connection with such a sale, we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser of your information honors your opt-out requests, if any. We will also make reasonable efforts to notify you of the purchaser.

#### Cookies and Tracking Technologies

As is true of most websites, our Site gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.

We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you, to improve marketing, analytics, or site functionality.

Technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags and scripts may be used by Life Storage and our marketing, analytics and other service providers. These technologies are used to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our Site user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these service providers on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information. You can choose to not accept cookies, but you may not be able to use some features of the Site.

Some Life Storage business partners (e.g., advertisers or tracking utility companies) may use cookies on the Site. Life Storage does not have access or control over these cookies. For example, Life Storage utilizes Google Analytics, a common website analytics tool. For more information about Google Analytics, please refer to the website, "How Google uses data when you use our partners' sites or apps" at <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>.

#### Online Tracking / Do Not Track

Life Storage does not track you across third party websites and therefore we do not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals. However, some third party sites do keep track of your browsing activities when they serve you content, which enables them to tailor what they present to you. Life Storage may subscribe to these third party services in order to provide targeted advertising. If you are visiting such sites, your internet browser may allow you to set the DNT signal on your browser so that third parties (particularly advertisers) know you do not want to be tracked.

#### No Collection of Children's Personal Information

The Site is intended for audiences at least 18 years old. Life Storage does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. Life Storage reserves the right to delete any information we believe to be in violation of this Privacy Policy.

#### Security

The security of your information is important to us. When you provide sensitive personal information (such as a credit card number or a Social Security number) on our online registration or order forms, we take steps to protect such information from unauthorized disclosures. We implement reasonable electronic, procedural and physical security measures to protect our customer's personal information. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, therefore, we cannot guarantee the absolute safety of your data, and you transmit data to us at your own risk.

In the event of a breach of personal information we may notify customers to ensure you take the appropriate measure of protection, in compliance with applicable legal obligations. By using the Site or providing personal information to us, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security issues.

#### User Access and Choice

If your contact or other information changes, you are responsible for correcting or updating your information by making the change on your member account information page or by emailing our customer service via our contact us form. We will endeavor to respond to your request within ten (10) days.

If you would like to change or terminate your subscription to any Services, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove, or deactivate your subscription by making the change on your member information page or by emailing our customer service via our contact us form. We will endeavor to respond to your request within ten (10) days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as otherwise required to process payments for your subscription for the Services. We may also retain and use your information as we deem necessary to comply with our business or legal obligations, and to resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

We will provide you with access to any personal information held about you within thirty (30) days of any request for that information. You may request this information from Life Storage by using the contact information provided above. Unless it's prohibited by law, Life Storage will remove any personal information about you from our servers at your request. There is no charge for you to access or update your personal information.

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions included in each of these emails, accessing your email preferences in your account settings page or you can contact us.

#### Site Referrals and Career Opportunities

The Site may allow you to use our referral service to tell a friend about the services offered through the Site or to refer a friend to a job posting on the Site. If you choose to use this service, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Site or to view a job posting available on or through the Site, depending on the referral service you select. Life Storage uses this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. 

#### Links to Third Party Sites

The Site includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Life Storage. If you submit personal information to any of those websites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit. 

#### Blog / Forum

The Site may offer publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your information from our blog or community forum, contact us. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

#### Social Media Widgets

The Site includes social media features, such as Facebook and Twitter buttons. These features may collect your IP address, which pages you visit on the Site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Life Storage may also maintain presences on social media platforms like Facebook, Twitter, and LinkedIn. Any information, communications, or materials you submit to Life Storage via a social media platform is done at your risk without any expectation of privacy. Life Storage cannot control the actions of other users of these platforms or the actions of the platforms themselves.Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

#### Location of Information

Life Storage has servers and/or offices located in the United States, so your information may be transferred to, stored, or processed in the United States. By using the Site, you understand and consent to the collection, storage, processing, and transfer of your information to Life Storage facilities in the United States, and those third parties with whom Life Storage shares it as described in this Privacy Policy. 

#### No Liability

You understand that electronic communications may be accessed by unauthorized parties when communicated across the Internet, network communications facilities, or other electronic means. You agree that Life Storage is not responsible for any electronic communication and/or any of your personal data which may be lost, altered, intercepted or stored without authorization during the transmission of any data whatsoever across networks not owned and/or operated by Life Storage. Life Storage does not guarantee that your information will not be misused or disclosed to third parties. Life Storage will not have any liability to you for any such misuse or disclosure. 

#### Consent and Notification of Privacy Policy Changes

By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy and to our information gathering and dissemination practices. If we decides to change this Privacy Policy, which we may do at any time without notice to you, we will post those changes on the Site. We suggests that you periodically check the Site for changes to this Privacy Policy. You are responsible for periodically reviewing our Site and this Privacy Policy to check for any updates or changes. 

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us:

  * Life Storage
  * 6467 Main St.
  * Williamsville, NY 14221
  * (716) 633-1850
  * Effective as of February 7, 2018

Doc #01-3059614.3
